[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
You know, maybe I SHOULD keep moving,
because they probably WILL teleport
behind me, then collapse the building.
Then, they win because they're
aliens, so who cares, and I'm dead.
So, is this the reactor room or what?
It looks pretty flooded to me.
Jeez, that's a lot of blood on the wall.
I don't think the aliens did that.
The splatter velocity's too high.
Oh, there's an entrance there.
Shit, that's kind of deep.
I guess this suit lets me sink
down pretty fast.
I don't know.
The stakes are pretty high,
but--Oh, my God!
How did I not see this? Am I blind?!
This kit might have morphine!
Yes, here it is! Morphine sulfate!
Aahhh...
Yeah, I'll start feeling this soon.
Oh, my God, did I need this!
This is fucking perfect.
Alright, let's get the blood
flowing so this kicks in!
A cold swim should do just the trick.
Time to go save the world!
[underwater mumbling]
[gasping]
I don't think I'm feeling it, yet.
Maybe... I don't know.
"Radiation".
Well, I'm either getting a
little bit or a lifetime supply.
[inhale]
[underwater mumbling]
Well, this COULD be the reactor.
Honestly, we own so much huge
machinery, I have no idea.
[underwater straining]
[underwater panicking]
Okay, that's partially flooded.
Soon, I'll get back to long-term panic
instead of all this short-term panic.
[underwater straining]
It's flooded! I'm a hero!
[vortigaunt charging up]
What the hell?
Man, fuck you!
I just saved your life from a
meltdown, I'm a hero!
You can't zap me like that, I'm a hero!
Yeah!
Jesus.
Electricity does not respect my heroism.
Well, I guess climbing out of
here is a good idea, right?
Right.
I don't get it.
Why is there so much arcing-BLAAAAH!
AAAH! AAAH-AAAAH-AAAAAH!
Huh, maybe being on a metal
ladder isn't so smart, either,
especially since I'm still wet?
Uhh...
Okay, I didn't feel much.
I guess my boots have some insulation
in them. Or maybe it's the morphine.
Hmmm.
Alright, time to go jump the--
[shuddering, screaming]
Shit, I think I made a mistake.
I don't think I flooded the reactor;
I THINK THIS IS THE GENERATOR, GOD DAMMIT!
WHY WOULD THEY FLOOD THAT?!
THAT WOULD JUST BE
DANGEROUS AND BREAK THINGS!
GRRAAAAAAAAAAGH!
GOTTA GET OUT OF TORTURE CHAMBER!
I DON'T NEED ELECTROSHOCK THERAPY!
I ALREADY HAVE MY--YAAAAAH!
Fucking shit!
I'm getting out of here before
it melts through the door.
I'm feeling pretty good, though.
I haven't felt this good since...
yesterday when I got to the surface
and thought I was going to leave.
Except then the military started
bombing the place, then I felt... bad.
Hey, "Supplies", I like supplies.
[Geiger counter ticking]
Okay, not the radioactivity.
I have enough of that. Thank you. No.
Hey, this looks civilized.
Where does this go?
Up.
Okay, where's the button?
Oh, there is no button. It must
be on the outside.
[button buzzes]
We design a lot of elevators like that.
Oh, I see. The button doesn't work.
We design a lot like that, too.
Okay, I can climb.
An old-fashioned elevator.
The kind that's powered by... ladders.
[metal groaning]
What was that?
Well, where's the...?
Oh, come on, guys.
You can design this better.
All right, I'm...
Batman.
Yeah-ha-ha-ha!
Yeah, this is great.
"SUPPLIES"!
I like supplies.
Let's get some supplies.
Oh, wow, more drugs.
I-I don't know. I'm feeling
pretty good now.
Okay, I'll take this.
That's... yeah.
I don't know. I might overdose.
What do you think, Mr. Crate?
Yeah, you always know what to say.
I'd better play it safe.
Oh, wow. What the fuck are you?
GUARD: Sir?
You're blue.
That's a tragedy, really.
You look like all the others.
I should go and fix that for you.
GUARD: I'd like to get my hands--
Stop mumbling.
GUARD: Hey, Gordon.
Oh, wow. You know my name.
That's amazing.
Well, you SHOULD! I'm a hero!
Ooooh!
GUARD: Yep, all that target
range time is gonna pay off today.
You're right. Why fight temptation?
[health charger beeps]
Yeah, I can handle some more...
I'm a hero!
HEV: Morphine administered.
Fuck, yeah!
I am ready to face everything!
I'm feeling a little drowsy,
but that's cool.
I'm very chill.
What's this?
Okay...
I think I just watched some guy kill
himself by walking into the portable sun.
I didn't know we had one of those.
Or that they even existed.
Whoooaaaaaah...
Wake up time!
Hah! I didn't even feel that!
Hey, how are you doing?
I feel great!
Hey, I've gotta ask you something...
What do you know about nuclear fusion?
Nothing, right? Yeah, I didn't think so.
Oh!
Now, YOU...!
I know YOU don't know anything.
Hey, listen, these monsters are
interrupting my train of thought.
So, you need to talk to the administrator
and tell him to stop it, all right?
Just stop it.
We've got enough monsters for
at least nine weeks.
This is total overkill.
[straining]
I was meant to turn this...
That did... something.
"Radiation Hazard"--they're bluffing...
Raaaah...
I wanted to see the portable sun.
How did we do that?
That's fusion power!
And we have it here all
tucked--Whoooooah...
Oh, shit... no. I don't
think I trust this, yet.
It glows.
Buttons!
[tapping buttons]
No...
Jesus Christ! What am I looking at?
Is this a star?
Did we create a fucking
star in a box somehow?
I didn't feel any heat off it.
Did we figure out cold fusion?
Cold fusion has been the butt of physics
jokes forever; it's an embarrassment.
Isn't that in the Journal of
Irreproducible Results?
But, you know what?
I bet those guys didn't have spinning
energy balls just hovering and...
trying to read my mind.
Why am I seeing more of these down here?
This is obviously just a storage area.
Maybe I took too much morphine...
But, fuck that! I can walk and everything.
And I feel so good!
Buttons!
Zooba-dabba-dooba-dabba-dabba-da!
It's cold fusion; how come I'm
not in this department?
There must be an explanation.
This is my explanation?!
I don't understand!
This is too interpretive.
I don't have to take this, I'm a hero!
Hey, are you an oracle?
No, you don't look like one.
Hey, this is just like Dirty Harry.
A long-range scene.
No, wait. It was one of the sequels.
That's my favorite Dirty Harry movie.
The one where he guns down the
giant monster with the tentacle arms.
"Make my day, squidface."
Ehh, you're not as big
as the one in the movie.
I feel like skipping through the hallway.
It's a nice big one.
Oh, what's in here? Awww.
Maybe I won't skip. It's kind of
heavy with the suit and the guns...
...and the bang...
...and more bang...
...bang-bang...
...and kaboom...
...and... oh boy...
Blaaaaghaaghgagh!
Bugs...
Man, you guys made
this hallway all dirty.
Why did you do that?
It was nice and squeaky clean
before you showed up.
It made me want to roll around in it.
I don't want to do that anymore.
Well, this is a little better.
Where my lab at?
[door buzzes]
Bahh!
Ah, okay, I think I figured out
what this place is.
This is where we take all the
VIPs looking to fund the place.
There are labs but they're all a
little too clean.
Oh, shit, not this one.
What the hell happened here?
That splatter mark looks like
this guy fell two stories.
How does somebody trip like that?
[Geiger counter ticking]
And we're leaking radiation;
this is not part of the tour.
But, yeah, we take the VIPs
here, show them the energy balls,
they don't know anything so they're
impressed and give us more money,
when the reality is they're
holograms. I'm sure of it.
Yeah, see, look at that pad
underneath; these are holograms!
Wow. A lot of them.
Those rotating platforms are cool, too.
Yeah, this would impress the hell out
of me if I didn't know anything.
In fact, it STILL impresses me,
because I'm kind of high?
Yee-hahahaha...
Oh, wow, this looks dangerous.
Yeah, there's a certain percentage
of the public that believes,
unless you have robots or glowing
lights, that science isn't happening.
But, we have BOTH. That's why
we're so well-funded.
Some people expect chemistry
sets and dry ice fog,
but I think we have some
rooms for that, too.
Okay, I'm going to test my theory
like a TRUE scientist on drugs.
Da-DAH!
I didn't feel anything. At all.
Okay, I'm going to walk...
Yeah, it's totally a hologram!
Heeehhhh...
Well, I could stare at these a long
time, the way I'm feeling right now
but I still don't know where
[bzzt]